Dance to your own beat.
Work It is a comedy, music film directed by Laura Terruso.
A brilliant but clumsy high school senior vows to get into her late father's alma
mater by transforming herself and a misfit squad into dance champions.
Quinn Ackerman, played by Sabrina Carpenter.
Jasmine Hale, played by Liza Koshy.
Isaiah "Juiliard", played by Keiynan Lonsdale.
Ms. Ramirez, played by Michelle Buteau.
Jake Taylor, played by Jordan Fisher.
Charlie, played by Drew Ray Tanner.
Work It is a 2020 American dance comedy film directed by
Laura Terruso and written by Alison Peck.
Produced by Alicia Keys, Leslie Morgenstein and Elysa Koplovitz Dutton, the film stars Sabrina
Carpenter, Liza Koshy, Keiynan Lonsdale, Michelle Buteau and Jordan Fisher.
About a group of high school students of different backgrounds, the film
follows their journey to win the titular Work It dance competition.
The film was released on Netflix on August 7, 2020.
The film explores themes of high school, dance competition,
teen movie, interracial romance, playful.
The tone is lighthearted.